freeslide.com 2006-04-14

# FreeSlide

**FreeSlide.com Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy describes the privacy and data handling practices of FreeSlide.com, a website of FreeSlide, Inc. 

Please note, to become a FreeSlide.com member and participate in its membership incentive promotion, you must be at least 18 years old and a legal resident of the United States with a valid email and mailing address. If you do not meet these requirements, we ask that you do not complete the registration process.

**What Information We Collect/How We Use It**

We store and use the information you give us in accordance with the terms of this Policy. Our registration form requests that you provide certain contact and profile information (like your name, e-mail address, postal address, and phone number). Some of the requested information is required in order to receive FreeSlide Services; other information is optional. The required information is indicated as such on the registration pages of the FreeSlide Web Site. Depending on the specific FreeSlide Services for which a user registers, certain category specific information will be requested. We use this additional data to personalize your FreeSlide experience. By obtaining and using this information, we can provide you with the most timely, relevant and individualized service according to your preferences and interests.

Other than the information we require in order to provide one or more FreeSlide Services to you, you do not have to provide any further information. But your election to withhold certain information will limit the value of the FreeSlide experience for you.

In addition, we might receive information about you from outside sources and add it to your FreeSlide membership information. We do this to improve personalization of our services (for example, providing better newsletter content, advertising or special offers that we think will interest you).

We also collect information such as the identification of the server your computer is logged onto and whether you opened a FreeSlide e-mail delivered to you. We also may compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending identical messages to our members. You can add and modify any of the information you have provided by following the instructions set forth below.

We use all of this information in the following ways:

1.   to provide you with personalized information via electronic delivery and/or direct mail; 

2.   to send you targeted advertising via electronic delivery and/or direct mail; 

3.   to contact you for feedback and surveys via electronic delivery and/or direct mail; 

4.   to send you general and administrative information about your FreeSlide membership via electronic delivery and/or direct mail; and 

5.   to provide your contact information to FreeSlide marketing partners to allow them to send you special offers via electronic delivery and direct mail.   This most often occurs when you request that we do so such as when completing an online survey.

Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from customer lists, analyzing data, and providing marketing analysis. These agents have access to member personal information as needed to perform their functions for FreeSlide, but we do not permit them to use it for other purposes.

Right to Sell/License Data:  Freeslide may sell and/or license the personal information that you provide to us to third party businesses. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation, email marketing, and telemarketing.

Cookies. We may use cookies to, among other things, save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the FreeSlide Web Site. Many Web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You may change your browser settings to either reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is about to be placed on your computer. Please note, however, that rejecting cookies while visiting the FreeSlide Web Site may result in certain parts of the FreeSlide Web Site not operating correctly or as efficiently as if they were allowed. For example, if you are a FreeSlide member, you may need to enter your username and password each time you visit the FreeSlide Web Site.

Third Party Action Tags.  We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf.  These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifts or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness.  Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.  If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

E-mail Links. In some instances we may include certain links in our e-mails that will allow us to monitor whether you access specific content or advertisements contained in that e-mail. When you click on one of these links, we will record that click and certain activities on the Web page associated with that link. We may use this information for various purposes, such as to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior in and to our e-mail advertisements and content, and to better understand and serve you.

Disclosures. FreeSlide may disclose information about you and your use of the FreeSlide Web Site and the FreeSlide Services if FreeSlide believes such disclosure is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law or legal process; (ii) to protect or defend the rights or property of FreeSlide or others; (iii) to enforce the FreeSlide Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy; and (iv) to respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another. In addition FreeSlide may share or transfer information about you and that you provide to FreeSlide, to one or more third party entities pursuant to a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion, or all of, the assets or stock of FreeSlide or its affiliated entities, or as otherwise provided herein. FreeSlide may also disclose information to allow third party business partners and affiliates deliver marketing offers to you, however we only make these types of disclosures if you request that we do so.
